Privacy Policy
--------------

Primate Labs Inc. ("Primate Labs") respects your individual privacy.

#### Scope of the Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy covers Primate Labs’ treatment of personally identifiable information that may be collected while you are on a Primate Labs’ site, when you order, download and/or use its products (e.g., mobile applications) or services or that is shared with Primate Labs by its business partners. This Privacy Policy is part of our \[Terms of Use\] if you are using Primate Labs’ site or part of the applicable end user license agreement if you are using a Primate Labs’ mobile application. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies not owned or controlled by Primate Labs or to people whom Primate Labs does not employ or manage. This policy also does not address non-personally identifiable information (i.e., mobile device properties, device software platform and firmware, mobile phone carrier) which we may use and disclose to provide and further develop our products and services. The policy specifically addresses the following areas:

* What personally identifiable information is collected by Primate Labs or by any third party through our site and/or via our products or services;
* How Primate Labs uses this information;
* With whom Primate Labs may share this information;
* What choices are available to you as a user of the site and/or products and services with respect to collection, use and distribution of the information;
* What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control; and
* How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

#### Information Collection and Use

Primate Labs is the sole owner of the information collected on this site or via our products and services. Primate Labs may collect information from you at the following three different stages.

First, we collect anonymous, aggregate information from all visitors to the site and users of our products and services. Second, Primate Labs collects personally identifiable information when you create Primate Labs’ account and when you order Primate Labs’ products or utilize certain services. Online account creation may require you to submit the following personal information: name, address, company information, email address, and phone number. For purposes of billing, you may need to provide your credit card type, number, expiration date and billing address for the card. Certain personally identifiable information is required if you subscribe to Primate Labs’ newsletter, or sign up to participate in a promotion, sweepstake or survey through the site. Primate Labs may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners.

#### Personal Information of Children Under 13

Primate Labs complies with the requirements of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) and the FTC’s Rule interpreting COPPA (16 CFR § 512). This site and Primate Labs’ products and services are not directed to children and Primate Labs does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information form children under 13 years of age.

#### Use of Your Personal Information

Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient and customized experience while using our site and to allow us to provide products and services to you. Primate Labs will never give your information to, or share your information with, any third party not affiliated with or owned by Primate Labs, except as permitted by law. Primate Labs will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:

* We have your consent to share the information;
* We need to share your information to provide the products or services you have requested;
* We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of Primate Labs to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us); or
* We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process or find that your actions violate the Primate Labs’ terms of use or any Primate Labs’ license agreement or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

##### Profile

We store information that we collect through cookies and log files to create a profile of our customers. A profile is stored information detailing how individual customers use the site. Collected information in a profile is tied to the customer’s personally identifiable information. However, your profile is used solely for internal purposes, to help us improve the experience of our customers. We do not share your profile with any third parties.

##### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file stored on the customer’s hard drive for an extended period of time. The cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. Allowing a Primate Labs cookie to remain on your computer makes it easier for you to log in to and use the site.

##### Log Files

Log files record internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, internet service provider (ISP) referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track a customer’s movement in the aggregate and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

#### Analytic Metrics and Other Technologies

Our products and services may contain third party tracking tools from our service providers, examples of which include Google Analytics and KISSmetrics. Such third parties may use cookies, APIs, and/or SDKs in our products and services to enable them to collect and analyze user information on our behalf. The third parties may have access to information such as your device identifier, MAC address, IMEI, locale (specific location where a given language is spoken), geo-location information, and IP address. We use analytics information for supporting business analysis and operations, business intelligence, product development and improving products and services. By using our products and services you agree that such analytics companies may collect and use data and information in accordance with applicable privacy policy for such company. Google Analytics privacy policy is found at http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. KISSmetrics privacy policy is found at https://www.kissmetrics.com/privacy.

#### Submission of Reviews

Primate Labs may use and/or disclose any personal data, including your identity, voluntarily submitted by you in connection with your review of Primate Labs or other products and/or services. You are responsible for any content you make available in such reviews and should keep in mind that anything you submit for posting by Primate Labs may be made available for others to see. You should therefore carefully consider whether you wish to submit personal data, or any data, for these purposes.

#### Disclosure of Personal Information As Required By Law

We will disclose personal information when required by law, or if we have good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) comply with current judicial proceedings, a court order or legal process served on us, (b) protect and defend our rights, or (c) protect the rights, property, and other interests of our users or others.

#### Business Transitions

In the event that Primate Labs goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, our customers’ personal information may be part of the assets transferred. If, as a result of the business transaction, your personally identifiable information will be used in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, you will be given a choice consistent with our Notification of Changes section.

#### Links

This site may contain links to and portions of other sites. Primate Labs is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these other sites. When you leave our site or view a portion of a third party’s site through our site, we encourage you to read the privacy statements of each such site. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Primate Labs.

#### Security

Given the nature of the Internet and the fact that network security measures are not infallible, we cannot guarantee the security of your information. We use encryption to protect sensitive information online. The servers that store your personally identifiable information are housed in a secure environment.

When registering for access to a secure area of the site, we may ask you to select a username and password. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. We will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also, remember to sign out of the registered site and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence when accessing your computer.

#### Correcting, Updating, Deleting and Deactivating Personal Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, you may contact us to correct, update or delete and deactivate our record of your personally identifiable information.

#### Notification of Changes

Primate Labs may edit this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes, we will prominently post a notice on this page to alert you of the change.

#### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers who are California residents to request that Primate Labs not share their personal data with third parties for such parties’ direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, send an e-mail with “California Privacy" in the subject line to privacy@primatelabs.com or write to us at the address listed below.

#### Contact Information

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at privacy@primatelabs.com.
